Tonight at 11, my city will be confined once again,
therefore before that happens, I've come to the park.
Apparently there is a limited capacity of 13 people max.
Due to Covid.
Luckily, this morning rained
and there is none other than
two people and a dog.
Here there's some swings...
To be honest, I am not really good with swings
I get dizzy so easily...
Uyuyuyuyuy I'm getting dizzy.
Here there are some swings...
actually I don't really know what these are.
It's an excavator!
I need to get the hang of it.
This goes up and down... the excavators'... shovel-
And this collects the sand.
I must say I wasn't expecting that,
I wasn't expecting it to be an excavator.
Before I found this and I didn't really know what it was
so I stopped to take a look, do some research.
Apparently is like a water ride-
the only catch being there not being water.
If you lift this here
*technical difficulties*
the water falls this way and well, I am sure it's very pretty,
and then, before I was up there
and I thought it worked, but it doesn't-
This super cool metallic spiral, which is hollow on the inside
turns, and I thought it was going to get some of the water down there
and it was going to get in, and come up here
and up here it was going to come out this way
and come this way, this way and then it was going to pour over there or there-
but nothing happened, because as soon as it gets some water in
as soon as I fully turn it, it comes out again.
I'm only moving the water around.
My tripod!
Here, next to the water ride,
there is like a cute little shed
it's made out of wood-
Would you like something to eat?
no, thanks
I prefer this table over the picnic tables over there.
This are the other picnic tables,
there's my stuff,
and here we have a water fountain-
that of course doesn't work.
But look, here it says:
Drink here Madrid's water.
These slides are really nice because they are metallic-
What is not so good about them being metallic is that
in Summer, if the sun is really strong, you will burn your butt.
To go up these slides, you have several options:
some sticks,
some ropes,
a net
and some stairs.
I think you already know how stairs work,
there is no need for me to teach you how it goes.
You can also go up in freestyle mode, which I forgot to mention before:
[thrilling]
Finally we have arrived to my favourite:
the covered slide.
I will warn you that it's a little disappointing because at first it goes really fast but then it stops.
and forewarned is forearmed.
¡3! ¡2! ¡1! Go.
See?
Very well, let's go to the next and last part,
my favourite part, the zip line.
I can easily say without a doubt that the zip line
is my favourite part.
It's a lot of work...
well everything is a lot of work.
Let's hop on.
Set! Ready! And go!
(exaggerated 1)
my screams give me second hand embarrasment
I'm getting dizzy!
You don't really expect the impact by the end-
(exaggerated 22)
it lifts you very high above the ground.
This zip line has exactly the same seat
as the skiing lifts (they are called 'arrastres')
in the skiing areas:
you sit down like this, the cable up there moves, with-
with your skis and it moves forward, like this, uphill.
¡3! ¡2! ¡1!
Wait no.
I am going to run, and then get on the zip line, Ok.
¡3! ¡2! ¡1!